http://www.ournameismud.com/pages/privacy-terms

Shipping only $2.95 when you spend $40 (U.S. Lower 48 States)Order before December 13th to get your Christmas gifts via Ground Shipping!
Shopping Cart
Your cart is currently empty.
Continue Shopping
My Account
Welcome to Our Name Is Mud!
Privacy Policy
OurNameIsMud.com is committed to respecting your privacy. Since we respect the privacy of our customers, we have established this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”).
OurNameIsMud.com acknowledges the EU’s standard for personal data protection. OurNameIsMud.com has a need to extract and compile the personal data of employees and customers in the EU. This Policy addresses the privacy concerns of European employees and customers and the business concerns of the company.
We are providing you with this Policy to inform you of the kinds of information we may gather during your visit to OurNameIsMud.com; why we gather customer information; what we use the information for; under what circumstances we may disclose such information; and how you can instruct us to limit the use of that information. We may update our Policy from time to time, so you should review it periodically.
By using our Site you consent to the collection and use of information by us in accordance with the terms of this Policy. If we decide to change our Policy, we will post those changes on our Site and applications and notify you either by email, with a notification on OurNameIsMud.com, or by other means, consistent with applicable law. By continuing to use our Site after notice is given, you will have consented to our use of your information in this different manner.
This Policy does not apply to personal information collected from you offline or to third party web sites to which our Site may link. Your use of our Site is subject to this Policy. Please read this Policy before using our Site or providing personal information to us.
Note: You must be 18 years old or older to use our services.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
When you place an order on our Site, we require you to provide us with Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”). This information provides us the specifics of who you are and can be used to identify, contact or locate you. PII may consist of: your name, address, telephone number, email address, birth date, billing information, occasion type (Valentine's Day, etc.), products purchased, any relevant promotion code, and information and the recipient's name, address, telephone number, email address, and any other information you may provide us. We use PII for internal purposes, such as processing and fulfilling your order, confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration, analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services and offers, and developing new products and services. PII is compiled by us and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis.
We may retain e-mail or other communications you send to us in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve our services. To protect your privacy, you should not provide us with any information that is not specifically requested.
Our Site may collect information about your visit without you actively submitting such information. This information may include, for example, your browser type and language, your operating system, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the URLs of sites you visited before and after visiting our Site, the web search that landed you on our Site, and web pages and advertisements you view, and links you click on within our Site. This information may be collected using various technologies, such as cookies, Internet tags, and web beacons. Your Internet browser also automatically transmits to our Site some of this information, such as the URL of the website you just visited and the browser version your computer is operating. To protect against fraud and other misconduct, we may collect information about your interaction with our Site, which may contain account identifying information which only OurNameIsMud.com can decode.
When you provide information, including PII, to one of our brands, we may share that information with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with any OurNameIsMud.com brands. In addition, these brands may send you offers and promotions about their products and services. We will also share information, including PII, when consumers direct OurNameIsMud.com to share the information with third-party sites including, but not limited to social networking sites.
We may contract with third parties to provide services including, but not limited to, credit card processing, distribution, data management, etc. We may also ask third parties to fulfill your order. We only provide these third parties with the information needed for them to complete these services. We also ask third parties to confirm their security and privacy policies are consistent with ours, and do not authorize them to make any other use or disclosure of your information. However, please note that once we share your personal information with another company, the information received by the other company is controlled by that company and becomes subject to the other company’s privacy practices.
We may also use information, including PII, to communicate with you about your account or transactions and send information or request feedback from consumers regarding your website and changes to our policies; send offers and promotions of products or third-party products (including of other companies that are owned by OurNameIsMud.com); personalize content; provide consumers with targeted advertising based on your activity on our sites and applications and on third-party sites and applications; operate, understand, optimize, develop, or improve company’s sites, products, and operations, including by using guest survey research and analytics tools; and detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate the company’s policies or be illegal.
OurNameIsMud.com may disclose information, including PII, if necessary, in our good faith judgment, to respond to information requests from government authorities, to address national security situations, or when otherwise required by law. We may also disclose such information when OurNameIsMud.com reasonably believes that it is needed to identify, contact or bring legal action against a party who may be causing injury to or interference with OurNameIsMud.com’s rights or property, registered customers or potential customers of OurNameIsMud.com, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.
In the event of a sale or merger of OurNameIsMud.com or any of our businesses, our customers’ information, including PII and any other information we have collected as described in this Policy may be among the transferred business assets.
When you place an order, we will establish your own personal account where PII used in placing such order is saved. Your personal account is password protected from all third parties. You may access your personal account by requesting your password from us (go to My Account) and then signing in with that password. Afterwards, you may change your password, edit your PII, or request a password reminder at any time. Our database may store your billing and delivery information and will automatically transfer it to the order form each time you place an order so that you do not have to re-enter this information when you sign in at subsequent visits.
Within your personal account settings, you may opt in for our additional services. We may use your contact information so that you receive the full benefit of these services. You may view, edit, or opt out of these services at any time.
Your password will be your personal and confidential code to access your personal accounts on our sites. You may change your password as often as you would like.
Cookies
A cookie is a small file that can be stored on your computer's hard drive. OurNameIsMud.com uses cookies so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. You may be able to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. However, please note if you disable cookies, you may not be able to view all the pages or functions within our sites. Our cookies do not contain any personal information about you so OurNameIsMud.com will not be able to determine your identity. During your visit, we will record information regarding the number of visits you make to the various pages of our site. This information helps us determine the areas of our Site that are most attractive to our visitors, so that we can make improvements or add new features based on our visitors' interests.
Links To Other Sites
Visitors will find links from OurNameIsMud.com to independently-owned, controlled, and/or managed internet sites whose content may be of possible interest to our visitors. In many cases, but not always, the links represent cooperative projects or mutual links established with the organizations connected with these sites. While we initially visit these sites to which we directly link, please note that we do not control the content that appears on these sites and such content may be constantly changing. In addition, your use and your information received by the other company when visiting these sites is controlled by that company and becomes subject to the other company’s privacy practices.
Security
The security, integrity, and confidentiality of your information are extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative, and physical security measures that are designed to protect user information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use, and modification. We regularly review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.
Consumers are able to order online with the use of a credit card. In such instances, OurNameIsMud.com and its partners use secure server software over a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) line, the latest technology to protect your credit card information.
We urge you to keep any password that you establish with us in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place. You must promptly notify us if your user name or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will note that you have canceled your user name or password in our system and will update our records accordingly.
Control and Choices
You may opt out of receiving marketing emails. To stop receiving OurNameIsMud.com’s promotional emails, follow the instructions in any promotional email or message you get from OurNameIsMud.com.
You can control if OurNameIsMud.com shares information with third parties for its marketing purposes and for third parties’ offers and promotions. To opt out of having OurNameIsMud.com share your information with third parties for its promotional purposes, email us at privacy@enesco.com or call OurNameIsMud.com Customer Service at 1-800-436-3726.
You can correct, update, and delete your registration account by logging in to your account through the Site or by contacting OurNameIsMud.com.
You can request access to the information, including PII, we hold about you and you may request that we amend or delete the information.
Please be aware that if you do not allow us to collect personal information from you, we may not be able to deliver certain experiences, products, and services to you, and some of our services may not be able to take account of your interests and preferences. If collection of personal information is mandatory, we will make that clear at the point of collection so that you can make an informed decision whether to participate.
Data Transfers, Storage, and Processing
We operate globally and may transfer your personal information to individual brands of OurNameIsMud.com or third parties in locations around the world for the purposes described in this Policy. Wherever your personal information is transferred, stored or processed by us, we will take reasonable steps to safeguard the privacy of your personal information. Additionally, when using or disclosing personal information transferred from the European Union, we use standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission, adopt other means under European Union law for ensuring adequate safeguards, or obtain your consent.
Children
Our Site is intended for a general audience and is not targeted to or intended for use by children. OurNameIsMud.com does not knowingly collect or use any personal information from minors younger than 18 through our Site. We do not knowingly allow minors younger than 18 to order our products, communicate with us (meaning that we do not send e-mail correspondence to anyone who tells us they are under the age of 18), or use any of our online services.
Children under the age of 18 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any contact information to anyone online. If you are a parent and become aware that your child has provided us with information, please contact us using one of the methods specified below, and we will work with you to address this issue. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and supervise children's access to the Internet, and to help us protect children’s privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information without permission.
California Privacy Rights
Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year.
To request a copy of the information required to be disclosed pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact us using the contact information provided below.
While we do not allow individuals under the age of 18 to use our Site, if in error California users under the age of 18 do so they may request the removal of their content or information publicly posted on web sites or mobile applications by contacting using the contact information provided below.
Questions?
If you have any questions regarding the Policy, or would like to provide feedback to help us improve the Policy, you may contact OurNameIsMud.com through our Contact Us link on the navigation bar or by mail to the following address: OurNameIsMud.com Attn: Legal Department 225 Windsor Drive Itasca, IL 60143
Updates to This Policy
From time to time, we may change this Policy to accommodate new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements, or for other purposes. We will provide notice to you if these changes are material and, where required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent. Notice may be by email to you at the last email address you provided us, by posting notice of such changes on our Site and applications, or by other means, consistent with applicable law. If OurNameIsMud.com decides to change its privacy practices, an updated version of this Privacy Policy will reflect those changes and we will notify you of such changes by updating the effective date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.
Without prejudice to your rights under applicable law, OurNameIsMud.com reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy without prior notice to reflect technological advancements, legal and regulatory changes, and good business practices.
Any new policy will apply to all current and past users of our Site and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. Your continued use of our Site or other services constitutes your acceptance of the practices described in the revised Privacy Policy.
Privacy Shield
OurNameIsMud.com acknowledges the EU’s standard for personal data protection. OurNameIsMud.com has a need to extract and compile the personal data of employees and customers in the EU. This Policy addresses the privacy concerns of European employees and customers and the business concerns of the company.
OurNameIsMud.com is a participant in the Privacy Shield program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission and Swiss Administration. We have certified that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles with regard to our use of certain personal data. For more information about the Privacy Shield Principles and certification process, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield Web site here. This Policy applies to all personal data transmissions from OurNameIsMud.com operations in EU countries to the United States. This includes transmission of data over phone lines, computer lines, and in hard copy, and includes such material as payroll records, telephone records, business information, club membership information, performance evaluations, and any material that identifies a particular individual employee or customer.
The use of EU personal data will include global enterprise headcount reporting, statistical analysis, compensation planning and related transactions, career development, staffing, international personal security issues, internal investigations ethics investigations, law enforcement inquiries, U.S. Government agency inquiries, business planning and reporting, and mergers, acquisitions and divestitures.
Guidelines
OurNameIsMud.com has adopted the seven Privacy Shield Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer (transfer to third parties), access, security, data integrity, and enforcement with respect to personal data to be transferred to the U.S. from OurNameIsMud.com operations in the EU.
Notice – OurNameIsMud.com will notify employees and customers in the EU about the purposes for which personal data will be collected and used. Information will be provided on how employees and customers can contact OurNameIsMud.com with inquiries or complaints regarding personal data. OurNameIsMud.com will give notice to employees and customers regarding third parties to which it discloses the information, and restrictions that limit the information’s use and disclosure. In certain situations, data is “anonymized” so that the names of the data subjects are not known by data processors within OurNameIsMud.com. In these cases, data subjects do not need to be notified.
Choice – Prior to releasing personal data to a third party, OurNameIsMud.com will give an individual employee or customer the opportunity to choose whether their personal data is disclosed to that third party or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by that individual. For sensitive data, an affirmative choice will be given to the employee or customer if the personal data is to be disclosed to a third party or used for a purpose other than its original purpose or the purposes authorized subsequently by the individual.
Onward transfer – (transfer to third parties) – Prior to disclosing personal data to a third party, OurNameIsMud.com will apply the notice and choice principles, enumerated above. OurNameIsMud.com will commit to ensuring that the third-party keeper of personal data also subscribes to the Privacy Shield Principles or any other EU adequacy finding. OurNameIsMud.com will also enter into a written agreement with such third party requiring that the third party provide at least the same level of personal data protection as is maintained by OurNameIsMud.com.
Access – Employees and customers covered under this policy will have access to personal information about them that OurNameIsMud.com holds and will be able to correct, amend, or delete information if it is inaccurate (the exception is when the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks of the individual privacy in the case in question or the rights of persons other than the individual would be violated.) You can correct, update or delete inaccuracies by contacting OurNameIsMud.com’s Vice President of Global Human Resources at 1-800-436-3726, or at privacy@enesco.com.
Security – OurNameIsMud.com will take reasonable precautions to protect personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.
Data Integrity – Personal data kept by OurNameIsMud.com will be relevant for the purposes for which it is to be used. OurNameIsMud.com will take reasonable steps to ensure that the data is reliable and that it is applied to its intended use. OurNameIsMud.com will also ensure that the information is accurate, complete and correct.
Enforcement – OurNameIsMud.com is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, OurNameIsMud.com commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact OurNameIsMud.com at: privacy@enesco.com.
OurNameIsMud.com has further committed to:
Commit to cooperate with the Data Protection Authorities (DPAs) of the EU countries in the investigation and resolution of complaints and will comply with any advice given by DPAs;
Employ a procedure for verifying that the commitment the company has made to adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles has been implemented;
Remedy issues arising out of any failure to comply with the Principles. OurNameIsMud.com acknowledges that its failure to provide an annual self-certification to the Department of Commerce will remove it from its list of participants and the transfers of information will not be allowed unless OurNameIsMud.com otherwise complies with the EU Data Protection Directive; and
Disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
In addition, OurNameIsMud.com hereby acknowledges that under certain conditions, individuals subject to this policy may have the possibility to invoke binding arbitration for any dispute related hereto.
The OurNameIsMud.com Human Resources and Legal Departments will be the internal mechanism for ensuring compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles and facilitating the independent recourse mechanism referenced in the “Enforcement” section above.
Access to personally identifiable personal data of EU employees and customers will be to a limited number of users on a need to know basis.
Definitions
European Union – The European Union (“EU”) consists of 28 independent sovereign states: Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Poland, Portugal, Romania, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, and the United Kingdom.
Personal Data – (for the purposes of this Policy) – Any personal information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person who is a OurNameIsMud.com employee or customer and who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by a reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to his or her physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural, or social identity.
Self-Certification to the Department of Commerce – OurNameIsMud.com must certify to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it will abide by the Privacy Shield Principles. OurNameIsMud.com must also state annually in its published privacy policy statement that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles.
Sensitive Data – Sensitive data is data that pertains to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, income records, health, sexual orientation, or alleged commission of any offense. This data may not be transferred to a third party unless an individual gives explicit consent.
Responsibilities
Questions regarding the transmission of personal data from the European Union (EU) to the United States or any other non-EU location, or any further transmission of the personal data once received in the United States, should be referred to the Vice President of Global Human Resources at OurNameIsMud.com. That individual is responsible for maintaining this document.
OurNameIsMud.com must annually, in writing, certify to the Department of Commerce that it agrees to adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles.
Sign up for our newsletter and be the first to know about coupons and special promotions.
© 2020 Our Name Is Mud
